Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/ hungnguyenuet (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Java

Spring Framework
Object-Oriented Programming
(OOP)

Hùng Nguyễn

Software Developer at EWAY.,JSC Hanoi

Summary

Experienced Software Engineer with a demonstrated history of working in the internet industry. Skilled in Computer Science, Java, Teamwork, Algorithms, and Object-Oriented Programming (OOP). Strong engineering professional graduated from VNU - University of Engineering and Technology.

Experience

EWAY.,JSC Software Engineer May 2021 - Present (7 months) Hanoi, Hanoi, Vietnam

VNG Corporation Software Engineer June 2018 - May 2021 (3 years) Hanoi

EWAY.,JSC Software Engineer Intern November 2016 - February 2017 (4 months) Vietnam

Education

VNU - University of Engineering and Technology good, Information Technology · (2014 - 2018)

Activity

11/01/2021, Nga Lê (Lenka) added candidate to Java_mới chuyển việc

11/01/2021, Viewed by Nga Lê (Lenka)